Welcome to our final video of this experience.
The M.V.P. Accelerator is over, but is there development?
The most powerful message you can send is that development is a continuous journey,
not a one-time event.
The final part of the championship conversation is to plan the next season.
This solidifies the manager's multiplier effect by
embedding a culture of continuous growth on your team.
At the end of their final check-in, a coach simply asks,
this was a great season.
Based on everything you've learned, what's your primary focus for
the next 90-day season?
This question immediately frames their accomplishments as a foundation for
future growth, not a final destination.
Your play is to end your final conversation with that exact question.
What's the focus for your next 90 days?
Capture their answers in your playbook.
This becomes a starting point for your ongoing coaching relationship.
The ultimate challenge is this.
How will you take the frameworks from this program, the M.V.P. focus,
the 90-Day Way, the coaching for agility, and
embed them into everyday culture on your team?
What is your first move?
Now, go back to where we began this journey.
Reflect upon the one leadership behavior you wanted to strengthen for yourself.
How have you made progress?
And the one leadership behavior you wanted to improve for your team.
How did you see progress and
where did your 90-day plan support this journey?
As you move forward, I want you to think about this question.
Who will benefit from the leader you have become?
Your M.V.P. isn't just a blueprint for your own success.
It's a blueprint for the impact you will have on the world.
You are leaving a legacy and making an impact that other leaders will follow.
You have the opportunity now to put your name on the wall of fame and
share your own story.
This is how you inspire others through your journey.
We look forward to celebrating your success.
Thank you for your commitment.
You carry the weight of the workplace in many ways.
However, I am so proud of your commitment to your own leadership journey
that fuels the impact you have made on those you lead.
Leading from the inside out is where purpose meets performance.
The work you do as a coach matters more than you know.
It doesn't just build better employees, it builds better leaders.
And better leaders build a better world.
Keep going.
You've got this.
Now make it happen.